is asking us to simplify this crazy
thing if you look at a unit circle 11 pi
over 8 and 3 pi over 8 are not on the
unit circle so how can we simplify this
one piece of notes makes this very very
straightforward there are six sum and
difference formulas and this particular
one is the one that's going to help us
out here so looking at this we can treat
11 pi over 8 as a and three pi over 8 is
B and we can just rewrite this like this
here and then we can simplify inside the
parentheses 11 pi over eight minus 3 pi
over eight is eight pi over eight and
then we can bring down the rest of this
stuff and in fact a pi over a can
simplify to Pi so now we can use our
unit circle because Pi is on there so
there's several different ways to
evaluate this I just remember that on
the unit circle the tangent is the Y
value over the x value so at Pi it's 0
over negative one so the tangent of Pi
is going to be equal to zero and that's
it that's the answer to this question so
if you're ever stuck on a crazy looking
problem like this and you don't know
what to do chances are there might be a
very easy way to approach it and you
just might not know about it